You've been voted out.
I was going to say, nice to meet you, Brian, but I guess not.
You made it.
Great to see you.
My name is Cyrus.
Nice to meet you, Cyrus.
I am also son of two immigrants, came in legally.
I'm also Persian descent, born in LA.
Fantastic.
Tarangulese.
Yes, yes.
Well, I am mainly upset, not at the immigrants, legal or not.
I'm mainly upset at Wall Street.
I'm mainly upset at the elites, the special interests.
They are the main reason why we've been
having this issue since 1965.
And I understand most want to do well.
There are a few bad apples, we can agree.
But we want to go after the elites.
They are the main cause of the problem.
And just like health care, trade, everything.
Did you know, Cyrus, that the top 1%
pay, dodge $163 billion in taxes every year,
while undocumented people pay $100 billion in tax.
So I know where my anger is against.
There are issues with our tax system on the rich.
But in a state like California, some taxes are too high.
I used to live here, now I live in Las Vegas.
It's a different debate.
OK.
I'm saying immigration is good for America.
It depends on the taxes.
People like you and me, overall, are good for America,
is what I'm saying.
OK, but it depends on how it's done.
Yes.
It depends on how it's done.
And how it's being done to the US as well.
So I'm not blaming the housing crisis on immigrants,
not on wages.
But in a state like California that doesn't build enough homes
and they're bringing immigrants in,
you have to increase supply of housing.
I agree.
OK.
But this is where our anger is at, is at the political class.
I agree.
The Democrat Party used to have a different stance
on immigration 15 years ago.
Bernie Sanders, Hillary Clinton.
I'm not a fan of that.
I'm not here to defend different Democrats.
What I will say is that everyone here actually
does think immigration is good for America.
Everyone here uses an iPhone designed by an immigrant,
is on Gmail designed by an immigrant,
is on a YouTube show.
You guys all came to a YouTube show founded by an immigrant.
You wouldn't be here if it wasn't for an immigrant.
So you all love immigrants, whether you like it or not.
OK, but it is a taboo subject.
Should we be concerned about the demographics?
So Anglo-Saxon, European-American, 0%
of America, it doesn't matter.
Are they 0% of America?
Well, let's say if it becomes 0%.
It should not worry.
They're not going to.
Why are you bringing weird hypotheticals?
But there has to be.
I mean, they're still part of our country.
There's culture.
I mean, even Britain, like, it concerns me.
But it concerns me when Britain is changing.
And it's like they're losing their culture.
But it's losing their culture.
Are they?
Are they going to try to?
I'm from the UK.
I'm telling you, no one's losing their culture in the UK.
London is going to be very little British in one day.
What's the plan?
That's what we want to know.
You just made that up.
Have you been to London?
But how do we know?
Cyrus, have you been to London?
No.
So then maybe you shouldn't comment on places
you don't know anything about.
But what's the plan?
I grew up in London.
London's a very British city.
I was in London a few weeks ago.
OK.
It's a very British city.
I hope not.
I understand that there are people
in this audience that don't like me or you in this country.
And I respect that.
There's some that don't even want me to date a blonde woman.
They want to keep to their own, or ginger, or whatever.
I respect that.
But there has to be a deal made.
There's Idaho.
There's Montana.
They can go live in a homogeneous society.
I don't believe in force.
OK?
And I believe that there has to be a deal made.
And I think there's upsides and downsides to diversity.
There is a deal made.
People have elections.
They vote for elections.
And right now, there's Donald Trump in the White House,
not someone I support, but people voted for him.
Well, why did he get in, mainly?
Because we had 2016, Bernie Sanders.
OK.
Part of the reason he got in is that people in this room
want people like me and you to leave.
And they voted for him to try and make that happen.
I'm not surprised.
One of the Charlottesville marchers doesn't like me.
And I've met those people.
And I respect their views.
You really shouldn't.
Well, there are lots.
Don't respect racists and fascists, is my advice to you.
Well, they have their preferences.
You know?
That's just, we can't change that.
Actually, we can.
That's why I tried to come in today, but anyways.
All right.
That's time.
Please return to your seat.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Great pleasure.
My final claim is that Donald Trump's plan for Gaza
is ethnic cleansing.
Hey, how are you?
Hi, I'm Sarah.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
So why do you say this is Donald Trump's plan?
Why do you think that?
I mean, he says it's his plan.
Have you seen his plan?
Have you heard his plan?
He said it standing next to Benjamin Netanyahu
in January, February.
He said it on Fox News in an interview on Fox.
He said it on Air Force One when he was chatting to reporters.
Like, word for word, what's an example of what he said?
Word for word, he said, for example,
we're going to clean out the Gaza Strip.
He said they're going to leave.
We're going to take control of it.
He says, we'll own it.
I would own it, he says.
I'm not sure under international law
how he can own a foreign piece of land.
And when he was asked on Fox News,
the people, the Palestinians who are being forced to leave,
would they be able to come back?
He said, no, they wouldn't.
That is the literal definition of ethnic cleansing,
according to a UN definition of ethnic cleansing.
Why do you think that Trump is saying this?
Do you think that he has some personal interest in cleansing
Gaza, or do you think there might
be some special interest group, or perhaps religious
or ethnic group, that maybe he received money from them
and that's the whole reason why he wants to cleanse Gaza?
Or why do you think that is?
I don't do Donald Trump's motivations.
I really don't care.
My claim is that what he's doing is ethnic cleansing.
Well, don't you agree with that?
I would actually, yeah, probably agree.
But I'm just asking.
You agree that it's ethnic cleansing?
You agree with doing ethnic cleansing?
No, I don't agree with it.
But I agree that's probably his plan.
But I'm trying to figure out, why do you think that is?
Because Donald Trump's a white man.
He identifies as Christian.
I'm not sure if he really is.
But what interest does he have in preserving
a Jewish ethno-state?
Why would he have that?
That's a good question.
You'd have to ask Donald Trump that question.
I've got multiple views.
I'm sure you have many views.
I'm not sure I like where you're going with your views.
But I think Donald Trump is definitely
someone who's got financial interests in ethnic cleansing.
He's got political interests.
He loves the evangelical voters he get.
A lot of Christian evangelicals like to support Israel
because they think Jesus will come back
if all the Jews are gathered in one place with no Palestinians.
I think he's going to make money,
he thinks, from beachfront property with Jared Kushner.
He said something similar in the past.
You think that's the real reason?
I think there's multiple reasons, yeah.
I think financial, geopolitical, ideological, evangelical.
I don't really care.
My claim is that what he's doing is ethnic cleansing.
Ethnic cleansing is a war crime, according
to the Fourth Geneva Convention.
It's against international law under the Rome Statute.
So we shouldn't be part of that.
The United States should not be supporting Donald Trump's
plan for ethnic cleansing.
I agree.
What do you think should be done instead
with the Israel-Gaza situation?
I'm not sure what your stance is on this.
I would like to see a ceasefire in Gaza.
Ceasefire, a two-state solution type thing.
I don't really get into debates about what solutions.
I would like to see an end to the killing.
I would like to see Gazans have freedom.
I would like to see the Palestinians in Gaza
somehow get their land back.
80% of Gaza right now is under Israeli military control
or displacement.
I would like to see freedom for the Palestinian people.
I'm an American.
To go back to the core of this show,
I support American values, one person, one vote,
free speech.
It really is a religious and ethnic battle.
It is not, a religious battle.
Well, yes, that is what it is.
Obviously, between Jews and Muslims,
both want control of the Holy Land.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
What else?
What other?
Actually, the founders of Israel were secular.
They were not religious, actually.
I think some religious Jews, like Bezalel Smotry,
who's the Israeli government minister,
is a religious fanatic.
But the core of the conflict is over land.
It's colonial.
It's historic.
It is not about religion.
Colonialism is for a reason.
The people who want to steal the land
want everyone to believe it's religious.
My point is, why are we sitting here?
Why are we sitting here?
It's like a false dichotomy, where we have to argue,
do Jews get Israel?
Do Muslims get Israel?
Why are we?
I've never brought up anyone's religion.
How many of us here are Christians
trying to pick sides between Jews and Muslims
taking over Israel?
Don't you think that?
Hold on.
First of all, I didn't bring up religion.
Second of all, you know that a lot of Palestinians
are Christian, right?
Some of them.
You're just reducing it to Muslim versus Jew.
It's majority Muslim, yeah.
It's very small percentage.
But there are many prominent Palestinian Christians.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, but there's not that many of them.
So it's not worth reducing everything to religion.
The reason, why do you think Iran
is backing proxies that want to take over Gaza,
back the terrorism in Gaza?
It's obviously because they want to Muslim control of the land.
You don't think that's why?
I don't think it's about religion.
I've been following this conflict for decades.
It's not about religion.
People who say it's about religion, it's a distraction.
Well, it's a big part of it, I think.
I think it's become a big part of it.
It's been weaponized by bad faith actors, sure.
But I don't think that's the core.
One group of people are dominating another group
of people.
It is apartheid.
But what group of people is dominating
another group of people?
One ethnic group is dominating another ethnic group.
What ethnic group?
Jewish people.
Yes, dominating.
Arabs.
Yes.
But I didn't say anything about Christian, Muslim, Jew
in a religious sense.
Jews defined as religion and ethnicity.
You know that, right?
Well, why do you think that Muslims
want control of the Holy Land?
You keep saying Muslims.
I didn't bring up Muslims.
Well, they're Muslim states.
What do you think Iran wants to do with the Holy Land?
I didn't bring up Iran.
But that's part of the conversation.
What do you mean?
No, it's not.
The conversation is Donald Trump is doing ethnic cleansing.
And you agree with me.
So I'm not sure why you're still here, to be honest.
But it's part of the larger context of the conversation.
It's a weird debate when you actually agree with me.
What I was trying to say is we kind of have this false
dichotomy here, where we're trying
to take the side of the Gazans, which mostly it's
a Muslim majority, or the side of the Jews to try to decide
who gets control over Israel.
I didn't say anything about control.
I said don't ethnically cleanse.
America is a majority Christian country.
Should we be deciding Christians should have control
of the Holy Land?
I agree.
Donald Trump should not.
Nothing to do with religion.
Donald Trump should not be deciding what happens to Gaza.
That's my claim.
If you agree with me, great.
Let's shake hands.
Give the seat to someone who disagrees with me.
So are you saying, do you think that America should just
cut ties with Israel altogether?
What's your definition of cut ties?
Like stop funding them, stop being their military arm?
Yes, yes.
I'm on record saying that.
OK.
That was an easy end of that.
Whoa.
Welcome back, Richie.
You really want to be here.
First of all, I really thought that, obviously,
where we started, where it ended up,
there's a lot of aggression.
I can see in your eyes there's a level of exhaustion
from being here.